mercblogger.com 2010-08-22

# Mercenary Blogger | Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for this website. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

1.1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.

1.2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.

1.3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.

1.4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

Information Collection, Use, and Sharing

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request,

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

We will not spam you nor cause you to get any spam.

Your Access to and Control over Information

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address given on our website.

Links  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
